

# **EXPERIENCE**

# Web Developer & UI/UX Designer

Jun 2020 – Present

Freelance

Designing and developing websites for local businesses. SEO, Domains and Hosting.

#### **Trainee Software Developer**

September 2019 - Jun 2020

shoe Zone Ltd, England

Programming in BIS, known as Mapper, working on new software project with development team, carry on courses: HTML5, CSS3, C#.

#### Team Leader

July 2019 - September 2019

shoe Zone Ltd, England

Supervising staff, training staff, management
Distribution Center departments (Goods In, Dispatch).
Filing daily reports to shift Managers, using multiple
Warehouse Management Systems inc: WMS, BIS Mapper.

#### IT specialist – administrator of network

October 2006 - May 2007

APJ Computer Systems, Poland

Solving problems with operating systems (MS Windows: 98, 2000 PRO, XP HOME, XP PRO, 2003 SERVER SBS); creation of companies' websites; intranet and extranet administration; technical advices in the marketing campaigns.

### Administrator of intranet, office worker

October 2006 - May 2007

Pamax-Pagacz evident company, Poland

Management of business software, supervision of intranet, computer service; cooperation with producers and suppliers; management of wholesale firm; monitoring sale; management and training of staff.

# Lukasz Kawecki

Junior Software Developer
Web Developer



# **PROFILE**

I'm a Engineer in computer science with extensive knowledge of networks (LAN, WiFi), operating systems and computer equipment - this is my profession from University. I am currently trained in software development, web development and UI/UX design. I have serious passion for web development and UI effects, animations and creating intuitive, dynamic user experiences. My goal is to become a full stack-developer in future.

I am known for reliability and transparency; valued for competence and creativity; pays special attention to details.

I'm definitely software and web development passion driven person. I learn quickly and I am a very organized, I can organize my time well and productively, which helps me learn and do work at the same time.



# CONTACT

52 Kirkwall Crescent LE5 2QB, Leicester

07305 063 233

kawagringo@yahoo.co.uk

www lukaszkawecki.com

https://www.linkedin.com/i n/lukasz-kaweckia990171b1



#### **EDUCATION**

# **Engineer of Computer Science**

Specialization: Computer networks

October 2003 - April 2007

**UNIVERSITY**: Academy of Humanities and

Economics in Lodz, Poland

## **Technical Degree**

Specialization: Computer Science & Mathematics

September 1998 - July 2003



HIGH SCHOOL: Human Rights Defenders in

Zelow, Poland



# **SKILLS AND ABILITIES**

The following are my best skills which I believe are applicable to the position I have applied for:

- 1. Programming
- 2. Logical and Structured Thinking
- 3. Coding in Multiple Languages
- 4. Databases SQL Server
- 5. Business Information Server (BIS know as Mapper)
- 6. M-netics WMS Warehouse Management System

# ¥ŧ.

# PERSONAL SKILLS

- 1. Ability to work by myself without the need for constant supervision by employees.
- 2. Able to work harmoniously with other members of the team.
- 3. Possesses great analytical and problem-solving skills.
- 4. Management, Supervisory skills, Team Leadership.
- 5. Human Physiology.
- 6. Human Nutrition.



# OTHER SKILLS

- 1. Full driving licence.
- 2. Polish Language.
- 3. English Language.



### **PORTFOLIO**

To view some of my recent work, please visit my personal website under section - Portfolio:



lukaszkawecki.com



# DIPLOMAS & CERTIFICATION

Available upon request;

or please visit my personal website under section - Licences & Certifications:



lukaszkawecki.com



## REFERENCES

Available upon request.



# INTEREST







